<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="help_default">Default Help.</string>
    <string name="help_map">The Map displays one or more routes.
        When you tap on any point on the map,
        you are taken to a list of routes that have stops near the point that you tapped on.</string>
    <string name="help_all">Displays all routes, alphabetically.</string>
    <string name="help_recent">Displays the routes that you accessed most recently.</string>
    <string name="help_nearby">Displays the nearest routes to your current location,
      or to a location that you previously selected by tapping on the map, or from a route stop.</string>
    <string name="help_schedule">Displays the schedule of the route for today or for a selected day.\n\n
The schedule begins and ends at midnight.</string>
    <string name="help_schedules">Select one of the displayed schedules to see the schedule for another day.</string>
    <string name="help_stops">
A distance in parenthesis is a straight line distance from the current location or from a reference location.
A distance with a + or - sign is a <i>route distance</i>, the distance along the route
from a reference location on the route.  A positive distance means that the stop is ahead of you.
A negative distance means that the stop is behind you as you travel along the route.
\n\n
The reference route location is the current location, if you are on the route,
or the closest route location to your current location,
or the beginning of the route.    
</string>    
    <string name="help_stop">
Displayed information for the selected stop.


\n\n<b>Straight Distance</b>\n
The straight-line distance from your location to the stop.

\n\n<b>Route Distance</b>\n
The distance from your location to the stop, following the route, i.e. the sum of the distances from stop to stop.

\n\n<b>Distance from Start</b>\n
The route-distance from the start to the stop.

\n\n<b>ETA)</b>\n
Expected Time of Arrival at the stop.

\n\n<b>Speed</b>\n
The average speed of the bus.

\n\n<b>Coordinates</b>\n
The latitude and longitude of the stop, as published by OASA.
</string>   

<string name="help_about"><b>To Επόμενο Λεωφορείο</b>\nCopyright &#169; 2012\nAlex Athanasopoulos\nalex@melato.org
\nhttp://metakinisi.melato.org
\n\n<center><b>Credits</b></center>
The route maps and timetables are provided by OASA and are available to the public from www.oasa.gr.
\n\nMost icons are from the bctango icon collection, by Bosky Cinek (http://boskastrona.ovh.org).  License: Creative Commons attribution share-alike
(http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/2.5/).
\n\n<b>Errors</b>
\n\nContact OASA to fix errors in its timetables and contact me to fix bugs in the application.
\n
If you notice a mistake in a route timetable (e.g. the scheduled departure time shown by the application
does not match the time posted at the start bus stop):
\n
1. Check www.oasa.gr to see if the error is in their data.\n
2. If so, contact OASA directly (by phone or email) and ask them to correct it.\n
3. If this application does not match the OASA website,
please contact me so I can fix the bug or update the application with the latest information from OASA.
</string>    
<string name="eula"><b>Athens Next Bus</b> Copyright &#169; 2012 Alex Athanasopoulos, alex@melato.org.\n\n
The application is provided as is, without any warranty about its fitness for any use or the accuracy of the information it provides.\n\n
The application uses data that are published by the Athens Urban Transport Organisation S.A. (OASA) at its website (http://www.oasa.gr) and are subject to the following terms of use (translated by the application author):\n\n
<b>OASA Terms of Use</b>\n\n
1.  The user of the application accepts that the use of the information provided is done at his own risk.  The application provides data for the Athens urban transporation system that is licensed from the provider Athens Urban Transport Organisation S.A. - OASA (http://www.oasa.gr).  Access to the relevant data is provided without payment.  In any case, the level of accuracy of the data is adjusted from the current needs and capabilities of OASA and may possibly not be appropriate for their use by third parties and for purposes that are not anticipated by OASA.  Therefore, all relevant data are provided \'as is\'.  Athens Urban Transport Organisation S.A. (OASA), ODIKES SYGKOINONIES S.A., and Urban Rail Transport S.A. (STASY), bear no responsibility whatsoever for any omissions or errors, in updating of the data and generally for any direct or indirect damage that could arise from using or operating this application.\n
2.  OASA has not contributed to the development of this application and bears no responsibility for its completeness or its compatibility with any operating system of a mobile or other device.\n
3.  The data published by OASA reflect, approximately, the current operational state of the Athens Urban Transport Network, which is subject to change at any time, without warning and without any liability of OASA, OSY, and STASY.  Interested parties may refer to OASA\'s website (www.oasa.gr) and/or call OASA\'s telephone information center (185) to get information for any scheduled or unscheduled changes in the operation of urban transport.\n
4.  OASA is the sole beneficiary of the intellectual property of the database from which the present application receives data and displays it in specially crafted graphical user interface.  The use of any logo and/or commercial trademark of OASA in the application\'s graphical user interface (GUI) or in the application icon does not mean that this application has been developed by OASA or its subsidiaries, neither that OASA recommends this application over other existing or future applications that will offer the same or similar features and information to the user.\n
5.  The export of data from the application and its import to any other application or computer code or database or any other organized dataset, digital or not, without the explicit written permission of OASA, is expressly forbidden.\n</string>

</resources>